When the silence comes
Guess it's f-
And you'll just feed back in the gap
Hello, Samantha. Hi, Barbara.
Who wants to do readings?
Let's start with a collective.
If you'd like one, you can just let me know.
Or if you're a member, you'll get a longer one.
Or if you'd like to donate, you'll get a longer reading.
I'll put my cash up if you'd like to.
Or a tip or whatever.
Everyone, what's up guys?
We'll do collective for the chat.
Uh-oh, a tower card.
Uh-oh, hold on, there you go, get the tower card.
Tower card is often, like this is probably
the recent path, there might have been a big shakeup.
It says they were young.
Healthy wealthy beautiful free and in love until tonight. Well, that's a little bit foreboding, but
We all have these tower moments sometimes
Shake-ups are good a lot, right?
Do we always rebuild? Oh
Six of wands this is a victory boat, but at what cost there we go. We have victory, but at what cost?
This is the card of victory.
And I think that that cost was the tower maybe, right?
That we had some kind of victory,
even though it did shake up something for us, right?
You may have looked bad at the time.
And then it's like, okay, well, before we won the pool,
this is starting on the new path,
starting over, starting fresh,
starting with a new perspective,
taking a leap of faith also.
This particular one just take the step
Does it it does appear to be off of a high place, but
You know you believe we have wings
Or do you believe you'll fall then we have night of wands, okay?
This guy's a hot head right we got the jack Nicholson the shining card passion
Impulse inspired action adventure, okay
Lots those are good things
Just because the deck is a horde deck don't necessarily think you know it's gonna be here's here's Johnny coming, right?
Oh, we also have five of
Five of wands. This is this is a competition
Maybe that competition you've won. Maybe it's maybe it's still gonna still go on after you after the victory, right?
But I see the five of wands and a more good nature competition more of like a team sports rather than a
individual kind of thing. Okay? But do watch out because there might be some
regret. Maybe like I find out if it's worth fighting. Because if there's
already a victory, is there a reason to keep going? To keep just recycling the
storyline? I don't know. We're recycling the storylines. I think we might regret
keeping going in the competition. How about just take your crown and win.
Queen of Cups.
Queen of Cups is well, you know, she's somebody that is mastered her emotions
Though I think has been very emotional
Okay, this might be you or it might be our styles or something
Hierophant in reverse
This is a going away from tradition. Maybe looking at something untraditional when an untraditional path
Also, I'm getting hangman vibes saying same things from a different perspective in terms of this higher source. Okay
Star this is the victory. They can't take away from you. Okay
Because you're the star the stars is over powers right hit the star of our powers
You know the Sun is a star too. You think you're Leo Aquarius energy there. Okay. I hope you guys like that
I hope and ghosts will be around soon
He's not
Seems like some people left so I'll play a couple of music videos
No one comes and I'll send it end it, but I
Have fun today guys
You say I crash out when I'm lying to and I thought what we had was sacred
I don't want to play that
The panels hum and the chaos spins
Lenor hisses, the mics all crack
The spirits log in, there's no turning back
Well guests crawl out of the digital grave
Cloud chasing ghosts with drama to save and die
Father sight, the cat daddy of doom
Light a candle in the livestream tomb
In the chat they chat my name
Typing Hill while they play their games
Superchats flicker like cursed coins
Every donor feeds the noise
Whispering gossip in my ear
They fight, they flirt, they rage, they cry
It's content, golden reasons
Why be to span the guards, the gate
Alexandra laughs, we sealed our fakes
Someone's mic peaks, the lights all fade
We dance with demons, we are ourselves made
Algorithms taste the fear
They feed the clips for all to hear
Like, are we safe tonight?
Safe.
Never but damn, we're live.
I was caught inside the storm of my own fear
Lightening struck and words fell sharp and clear
Didn't mean to let the thunder roll your name
I was reaching for connection, not to lay the blame
only in regret so thank you Alexandra for all you gave for the laughter the
light the way you stay if the road bends and you turn away
Just love that linger
You like it? Who sings it?
Call her.
Aye aye.
Aye aye sings it.
Okay, someone wants to come up all of us
say it for someone.
Hi sweetie.
Hi babe.
Question.
So I know you give away free memberships.
Right now I'm only on my phone.
Can we give memberships away on our phones?
You have to be on a computer. I think if it's um, it has to be like the Android though
It doesn't seem to work on my iPad stuff. So it's Apple. Okay. I have an Android
Okay, so Android. Yeah, it should just if you click on the regular
Dollar sign it should save membership gifting down there
It should pop up or if not then it should come if you go like
To my channel and slash members. I think that might work, but yeah, okay
All right, I'm gonna figure it out. I knew you did it. So I was like, wow, let me ask him
How are you? I'm ours. How's your how's your 24 hours is doing it guys? Be sure to go to summer hot mess summer
She's doing her 24 hour
On the street stream or your tent stream
she's
Out there doing outreach and particularly 24 hours and she's doing this special today
So make sure you go go over summer say hi. How's that going summer?
It's going good. I'm doing a fundraiser
I do it twice a year and so I stay in a tent for 24 hours and people order stuff up off our Amazon
Wishlist or they donate to us and we're doing pretty good so far
So I've been going since two o'clock
And I'll be here until two o'clock tomorrow and we'll be live the whole time. So yay
Please post your the link to the show or the channel whatever you want to do or both
You know, I want to make sure everyone supports you and
and goes over there too and so I'll be sure before I end today to direct everyone over there too and
I'm gonna say thank you for everything love you and thanks for the good work too summer love you
All right. Love you. I'll pop in later. I'm just gonna I was gonna go see if I can figure out how to do these membership things
See you later. Thanks for the help back
right
Yeah, there she goes. That's her. I think that's her link for today. And let's you know
Hello, I'm just kind of I'm kind of tired today again a little like a little stuff going on for me. So let's go over there
Celebrate her and and her cause and know her work and stuff and I'll be back tonight
I think ghost wants to do ghost sober tonight. So we'll do ghost sober later. Hey, Lenore, you want to say hi to everyone too? Okay?
Let's say hi. Do you want to cuddle with me for a little while under the cover is Lenore? Yeah
That's a good plan
But I'll turn on summers and we listen in okay. Oh
That's so good. Oh, oh, she's comfy. Yeah
The show over I know the show is over it's over early, but let's go say hi to let's go say hi to summer
I'm just like not at my hundred percent
I don't want to like be falling asleep or like, you know
Not here to like in my full capacity. So I'm sorry
But I'm gonna sort of check out the the vibe and we'll see you later guys. Okay
Yeah, it was 23 minutes I was on so a little little short shorty
Hey guys, but I want to thank everybody for support during this time
And I know I got a lot of people saying I'm like some kind of weirdo stalker
Obsessed person. They're like, oh look at these people. They're back. Like there's two sides of every story really, okay?
I'm I don't
Maybe occasion of overstep the boundary, you know to get some of the tension occasionally not in like any kind of like harmful
way or not ever trying to attack anybody I ever trying to like
bother anybody and I'm, and you can see I'm always,
I'm received oftentimes with like these opposite energies,
like, oh, okay.
Yeah, I love you.
I love you.
And then it's like, oh, don't talk to me again.
And it's like, without anything changing in the middle.
So when I'm constantly pulled back and forth with that,
just get to know that's confusing for me too.
And, but I'm making an effort not to,
and I'm making effort.
I'm just not,
Not going where I'm not wanted it right now. Okay, and stay in my lane. So I'm not bothering anybody
So you just think I'm some kind of weirdo stalker. You're the kind of miss
Informed about things and maybe you know, either lick listen for both sides of the story
or
You know
I'm ending the chapters of many some chapters of this book
Okay, so I won't be bringing things up.
So thank you for being here.
Appreciate you guys.
I'm just gonna go under the covers for a little bit.
Thank you.